(Amy:)Bye.
Oh! Good news, gentlemen.
(Sheldon:)Amy's at a conference
this weekend,
(Sheldon:)which means I'm available
to be entertained, hmm.
As today's youth might put it:
Who wants to get their Sheld-on?
(Howard:)Bernie and I are getting
the house ready for the remodel.
(Howard:)We could always use
an extra pair of hands.
(Sheldon:)That sounds awful. Raj?
(Raj:)Uh, I've got time booked in
the telescope room all weekend
(Raj:)scanning for rogue planets.
(Raj:)You're more than welcome
to join me.
(Sheldon:)That's the one to beat.
Leonard?
(Leonard:)Oh, if anything,
I'm trying to get my Sheld-off.
(Sheldon:)Well, then it looks like we have
a winner. Congratulations.
(Raj:)Well, I should warn you,
it's just looking at data
(Raj:)for hours and hours
on a computer screen.
(Sheldon:)Uh, stop selling it, kid.
You won.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪